<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_US" /><updated>2022-09-10T01:43:56+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Central New Jersey Democratic Socialists of America</title><subtitle>Homepage for the Central New Jersey Democratic Socialists of America</subtitle><author><name>mani_d2</name></author><entry><title type="html">Solidarity with Dr. Mosdell!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/solidarity-with-dr-mosdell/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Solidarity with Dr. Mosdell!" /><published>2022-06-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-06-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dr-mosdell-solidarity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/solidarity-with-dr-mosdell/">&lt;p&gt;Central Jersey DSA stands with Piscataway school psychologist and DSA member, Dr. Cassia Mosdell. Dr. Mosdell has been effectively fired through the denial of tenure because of her advocacy for LGBTQ+ and other marginalized students. At the May 12th Piscataway Board of Education meeting, students and parents of students of Theodore Schor Middle School spoke about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mycentraljersey.com/story/news/education/2022/05/18/students-back-piscataway-educator-effort-overturn-non-tenure-decision/9788459002/&quot;&gt;positive impact&lt;/a&gt; that Dr. Mosdell has on all students. Unfortunately, the Superintendent went through with his decision to deny tenure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a time when the LGBTQ+ community, especially children,  are under attack from those that would silence and erase them, Dr. Mosdell has been a cherished and powerful force for helping find their voice and identity. If the Board of Education does not overturn the Superintendent’s decision to deny her tenure, her students risk losing a beloved advocate and counselor. We must protect both the LGBTQ+ community and those who work hard every day to keep them safe. Losing Dr. Mosdell would be devastating to a vulnerable community and would stifle such advocacy everywhere that educators fear to be the victims of this kind of retaliation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stand in solidarity with Dr. Mosdell and demand that the Board of Education and Superintendent reverse this decision. We encourage all community members who are alarmed at the prospect of “Don’t Say Gay” laws coming to New Jersey to join us at the June 9th Board of Education meeting. We need as many people as possible to show up in support of Dr. Mosdell and her students on June 9th and to be prepared for future mobilization in support.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mani_d2</name></author><category term="labor, solidarity, lgbtq+" /><summary type="html">Central Jersey DSA stands with Piscataway school psychologist and DSA member, Dr. Cassia Mosdell. Dr. Mosdell has been effectively fired through the denial of tenure because of her advocacy for LGBTQ+ and other marginalized students. At the May 12th Piscataway Board of Education meeting, students and parents of students of Theodore Schor Middle School spoke about the positive impact that Dr. Mosdell has on all students. Unfortunately, the Superintendent went through with his decision to deny tenure.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smalllogo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smalllogo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Hopewell Starbucks Solidarity Statement</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/central-nj-dsa-hopewell-starbucks-solidarity-statement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hopewell Starbucks Solidarity Statement" /><published>2022-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/central-jersey-dsa-starbucks-solidarity-statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/central-nj-dsa-hopewell-starbucks-solidarity-statement/">&lt;p&gt;Central Jersey DSA sends our congratulations to the Hopewell Starbucks workers on their union election victory! They filed for their election on January 11 and in the months since then, they’ve endured union busting in their own store and watched their partners across the country experience blatant retaliation and firings. Central Jersey DSA members have been inspired by their courage and resilience, and some have begun the process of organizing their own workplaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hopewell Starbucks workers join Starbucks workers all over the country that have filed and won their unions. As our comrades in Richmond DSA wrote after the first five Virginia stores won their union elections, “Working class organizing, often through unions, leads to undeniable material changes in peoples’ lives. These range from closing the racial and/or gender wage and wealth gaps to giving families access to stable housing and healthcare.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starbucks Workers United has filed more than 80 unfair labor practice complaints against the company, in response to Starbucks’ union busting and retaliation against outspoken union organizers. We echo the workers’ call to Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz to follow the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sbworkersunited.org/new-page-3&quot;&gt;Non-interference Principles&lt;/a&gt; to enable workers to organize without fear of intimidation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anyone in New Jersey wants to get started organizing at their workplace, please reach out to any of the NJ chapters of DSA. Workers deserve to have a say in their wages and working conditions - and if we fight, we win!  #1U&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mani_d2</name></author><category term="labor, starbucks, solidarity" /><summary type="html">Central Jersey DSA sends our congratulations to the Hopewell Starbucks workers on their union election victory! They filed for their election on January 11 and in the months since then, they’ve endured union busting in their own store and watched their partners across the country experience blatant retaliation and firings. Central Jersey DSA members have been inspired by their courage and resilience, and some have begun the process of organizing their own workplaces.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smalllogo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smalllogo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>